卡尼尔·乌提斯
Kaniel Outis.
他和ISIL恐怖组织是一伙的
He's been working with ISIL.
你知道那绝不是迈克尔
You know that's not Michael.
我们还需要你
We're gonna need you.
！请人人视频停止使用人人影视字幕组译制作品。人人视频≠人人影视  望周知
■
到我死时就能好好休息了
I can rest when I'm dead.
我担心的就是这个
That's what I'm worried about.
我不会丢下迈克尔
I'm not leaving Michael.
我们不能在一个人身上孤注一掷
We can't risk all of it for just one man.
ISIL的军队已经攻破了关卡
ISIL has broken through the checkpoint.
萨那就要沦陷了
Sana'a is falling.
要么我们合作  要么我们一起死
We work together or we both die.
我向你保证
You have my word.
阿布·拉马尔才是波塞冬想放走的人
It's Abu Ramal that Poseidon wants free.
波塞冬派你来的吧
Poseidon sent you?
够了
Enough!
这家伙是谁
Who the hell is this guy?
他是我哥  当时在监狱里
He's my brother. Back at the prison...
我必须否认你  你当时在拍我的录像
I had to deny who you were. You were filming me,
不能让他们知道
and they can't know.
他们说阿布·拉马尔壮烈牺牲
Abu Ramal has been martyred.
整个ISIL军队
The entire army of ISIL
刚刚向我们宣战了
just declared war on us.
瞧瞧 坏人登场了
Behold the villain.
公用电话
我到镇上来买咖啡
I, uh, I ran into town to get some coffee.
-你需要什么吗  -不用了
- Do you want anything? - No. I'm good.
谢谢亲爱的  我这快完事了
Thanks, honey. I'm almost done here.
我一会儿到湖边见你  好吗
I will see you at the lake in a little while, okay?
好的  我们回湖边小屋见
Okay. I'll see you back at the house.
你老公吗
The hubby?
你从凯勒曼那得到什么消息了
Uh, what did you learn from Kellerman?
亲爱的  下面这个消息真的很难说出口
There's no easy way to deliver this news, darling.
怕你听了心碎
It's a heartbreaker.
情况并没有好转
Doesn't get any better.
他已经坏透了
He's rotten all the way to the core.
你一直都在跟敌人同床共枕  宝贝
You've been sleeping with the enemy, baby.
我不明白
I don't understand.
这俩猴崽子杀了凯勒曼  离开之后
I followed them two monkeys from Kellerman's house
我就一直跟着他俩
right after they put a bullet in him.
显然他不是我们要找的人[波塞冬]
Needless to say he wasn't our guy.
关于你家先生他确实说了一些惊人的话
He did say some pretty alarming things about your boy,
波塞冬  震惊世界的人
Poseidon, the world shaker.
这些还不够让我把所有事情联系起来
‭Didn't give me enough to put all the pieces together.
等等  等等  他们都说了些什么
Back up, back up, back up. What did they say?
雅各布是怎么说的
Jacob? His words?
我没法靠太近  听不清  但是我...
I couldn't get close enough to hear much, but what I did...
我确实听到了你和迈克尔的名字
what I did hear was your name and Michael's.
-没错  他们三个看起来很熟  -天哪
- Yes, they seemed pretty cozy, the three of them. - Oh, my God.
这就是个卑鄙的阴谋...  你去哪
It's a nasty bag of conspir... Where are you going?!
去找我儿子
To my son!
蹲下  蹲下
Stay down. Stay down.
又来一波炮击
It's another artillery strike.
但他们肯定是习以为常了
But they sure as hell are used to it.
快走  快走
Go, go!
真主伟大
Allahu Akbar.
我们将不眠不休
直到杀害阿布·拉马尔的凶手在我们脚下被碾碎
也门已不是避风港  他们必将灭亡
这是真主给我们的承诺
让唤礼员从屋顶
大声将这条信息传播出去
[伊斯兰教报告祷告时刻的人]
在萨那的男女们
谁把西方人交给我们  就能得到一千万里亚尔[4万美元]
出发  找到他们
在萨那的男女们
谁把西方人交给我们  就能得到一千万里亚尔[4万美元]
ISIL的人刚悬赏一千万要我们的人头
ISIL just offered ten million for our heads!
等等  待在这
Wait. Wait. Stay here.
我们必须远离街道  不然就死定了
We got to get off these streets or we're dead.
一千万里亚尔[4万美元]
Ten million rial?
这么多钱出卖你老妈的命都够了
You give up your mother for cash like that.
我买佛莱迪·摩克瑞的骨灰也就这些钱
It's about what I paid for Freddie Mercury's ashes.
这时候还拿佛莱迪·摩克瑞装逼  不是吧
Freddie Mercury now, really?
总比说有50万人要杀我们好得多吧
It's better than talking about 500,000 people looking to kill us.
快来
Come on.
找到了一个可以从长计议的地方
Found a place to figure out next steps.
走吧
Let's go.
现在你该告诉我发生什么了
This is the part you tell me what's going on,
整件事的来龙去脉
the whole thing.
不行  没那么多时间
No. Th-There's no time.
这个国家就要垮了
Country's about to fall.
你会得到你想要的答案的  我保证
You'll get your answers, I promise.
现在我们就快没机会了
Right now our window is closing.
我们需要...
We need to...
我们需要转换到下一个应急方案
We need to pivot to the next contingency.
-火车站  -北上
- Train station. - Get up to the north.
就那样出境
Exit the country that way.
四年间早已时过境迁
Things have changed in the four years
而你一直被关在奥杰吉亚监狱  迈克尔
you've been locked up in Ogygia, Michael.
不需要你的计划了
Your plan's redundant.
ISIL控制了北边  道路关卡和火车站
ISIL control the north, roads, checkpoints, train stations.
即使我们成功穿过了城市  这也是自杀
Even if we make it across the city, it's suicide.
不  你错了  这就像个"猜杯游戏"
No. You're wrong. It's a shell game.
[移动三个杯子  参加者须猜测哪个杯子扣着小物体]
你去那些令他们意想不到的地方
You go where they never expect you.
等等  你一路到也门来找他
Wait. You came all the way to Yemen looking for him.
你以为他走失了吗
You think he was lost or something?
得了吧
Come on.
你想活命吗
You want to live?
机场是唯一的选择
The airport's the only option.
机场被称为是通向外界的主干线
The airport's known as the main artery to the outside world.
是ISIL组织最先会关闭的地方
It's the first thing ISIL will shut down.
一小时前飞机还在飞  你有电话吗
Planes were flying an hour ago. You got a phone?
没有  但他有
No, but he does.
用来嗑完药  对着皇后乐队打飞机
Burned it up jacking off to Queen, though.
罪名成立
Guilty as charged.
此刻  钞票哥正想办法让大家上飞机
C-Note's organizing a passage on the flight as we speak.
不  我跟你说
No, I'm telling you,
我的计划行得通
my plan will work.
一旦  一旦你离开了萨那北部...
Once... once you leave the northern part of Sana'a...
够了  我们甚至都不该谈这个
Enough. We shouldn't even be talking about this.
放开我
Get off me!
你怎么还活着
How are you alive?!
在也门
In Yemen?!
你出了什么事  迈克尔
What happened to you, Michael?!
现在  你先告诉我这到底是怎么回事
Now, I'm not moving another inch until you tell me
不然我一步也不走了
what the hell is really going on here.
越 狱 第五季第五集
！‘人人视频   耐卡’ 无耻盗取我人人影视原创字幕并删除翻译名单 据为己有 可耻之极 ！
■
迈克尔·斯科菲尔德必须得死
Michael Scofield had to die.
我不得不制造我死去的假象
I had to fake my death.
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
原创翻译  双语字幕
离开
Go away.
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
这是我所做的交易的一部分
It was part of the deal I made.
如果我为一名叫波塞冬的卧底特工效命
If I went to work for a deep-cover operative named Poseidon...
m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
翻译     春天里的小熊   ABCpril   PiPi   徐棒棒
我们都会获得自由
we would all go free.
翻译     高庭玫瑰   肉   木浅   四月   宜九零
校对     & 普通特效      吃何何、一招、凤翅天翔
那时我们确实自由了
We were free.
校对       匡老湿打死也不爆照          木浅
我们被赦免了
We were exonerated.
不
No.
时间轴    姜姜  大葱  壬虚浪影   WEB版时间轴  何何
只是我们自以为是那样罢了
That's what we thought...
但我们错了
but we were wrong.
后期      吉吉   V2 后期   吃何何、一招、凤翅天翔
我娶莎拉几周前
A few weeks before I married Sara...
总监      吃何何、一招、凤翅天翔
波塞冬联系了我
I was approached by Poseidon.
你觉得我肚子大了吗
You think I'm showing?
我还没习惯呢
I'm not used to that yet.
我得... 我得告诉迈克尔
I got to... I got to tell Michael.
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
最新海外影视剧下载
-给你  汉堡马上就好  -喂
- Here you go. Burgers will be just a second. - Hello?
是的  我是迈克尔
Yes, this is Michael.
波塞冬告诉我凯勒曼并没有权限
Poseidon told me Kellerman didn't have the authority
或者司法权赦免我们的罪行
or jurisdiction to exonerate our crimes.
他利用这点作为法律上要挟的筹码
He used that as a legal fulcrum.
告诉我他能在法律的权限范围内
Told me he could put us all away for life
把我们关一辈子  除非...
within the mandate of the law unless...
■
人人词典
使用人人词典查词学习，美剧原声朗读与例句场景
Prison Break
除非我为他效命
unless I went to work for him.
在现在这种时候  他们到底能谈些什么
What the hell can they be talking about at a time like this?
我不知道
I don't know...
但大哥在听我想听的事
but big brother's hearing things I want to hear.
我们不能待着
We cannot stay.
我们必须现在走
We must go now.
或许我们不用
Maybe we don't.
你到底在说什么
What the hell are you talking about?
或许逃跑都只不过推迟了不可避免的宿命
Maybe all this running is just delaying the inevitable.
在这孤独而死  在家孤独而死[没分别了]
Die alone here. Die alone at home.
天啊  你需要个女朋友
God, you need a girlfriend, man.
那些声音朝着我们过来了
Those voices are heading our way.
他们就要找到我们了
They're almost on us.
这个波塞冬到底是何方神圣
Who the hell is this Poseidon guy?
一个变态
A psychopath.
中情局里一名不得志的政策专家
A frustrated policy wonk in the CIA
自认为他能比他的上司做得更出色
who felt he could do better than his superiors.
他在中情局内创建了一个叫"21号空间"的组织
So, he created a cell within the CIA called 21-Void,
执行他自己的情报行动
implementing his own intelligence operations.
而他需要我的帮助
And he needed my help
在世界各地把入狱的人救出来
breaking out people imprisoned all over the world.
恐怖分子
Terrorists,
持不同政见者
political dissidents...
叛变的特工
rogue agents...
如果我做了  你和莎拉  你们会自由
and if I did it, you and Sara, you'd go free.
抹掉你们的案底  但是...
Your record's expunged, but...
但是有个条件
there was a rub.
不允许我和你们任何人联系
I wasn't allowed to have contact with any of you,
包括我儿子
including my son.
迈克尔
Michael.
所以当时迈克尔·斯科菲尔德"死了"
So, Michael Scofield was dead and...
这些年我用了很多化名
over the years I assumed many names.
最近就是卡尼尔·乌提斯
Kaniel Outis... the most recent.
你为什么不告诉我
Why didn't you tell me?
为什么不联系我
Why didn't you reach out to me?
我别无选择
I didn't have a choice.
波塞冬的"意思"  表达得很清楚
Poseidon made that... very clear.
怎么回事
How?
最初  我拒绝了
At first, I said no.
我不肯干
I wouldn't do it.
没过几周  莎拉被关禁闭  被人打
Then within weeks, Sara was incarcerated, beaten.
所以我妥协了
And so I gave in.
我做的一切  都是为了家人
Everything I did, I did for family,
为了你  为了莎拉
for you, for Sara,
为了麦克
for Mike...
这样你们就不用
so none of you would ever have to spend another day
在监狱度日
inside a prison cell or...
或者亡命天涯
or live a life on the run.
看看我们现在的处境
Look at us now.
他们要开始搜查建筑了
They're starting to search the buildings.
-火车站  -机场
- Train station. - ‭Airport.
火车站
Train station.
萨那国际机场
所有乘客必须出示机票
All passengers must present a ticket.
这样可上不去飞机  我们得从那穿过去
Never gonna get to our seats. We need to go through there.
连飞行员都上不了飞机
Even the pilot can't get on the plane.
这机场全都是飞机
This is an airport full of planes.
-肯定还有其他的  -没用的
- There's got to be others. - It's no good.
今天这里的人会死的
People will die here today.
我们得想别的办法
We need another option.
-我的人  奥玛  -奥玛
- My man, Omar. - ‭Omar?
那个小滑头吗
That slippery brother?
现在能相信人可不容易
Trust is a luxury right now.
可以相信他  他能起一定作用
He can be trusted. To a point.
-他在沙漠那边的西海岸有关系  -不行
- He has connections on the western coast, across the desert. ‭- No.
林肯和迈克尔要来  这才是计划
Lincoln and Michael are coming here. That's the plan.
如果我们走了他们就不知道下一步怎么办了
They don't have a next move if we leave.
现在都还不知道他们在外面的什么地方
Now they're out there somewhere, God knows where.
你朋友来晚了  你看看周围
Your friends are too late. Look around you.
这机场可不是他们待的地方
This airport is no good to them.
我们不能走
We're not leaving.
那是什么地方
What is that place?
那些西方人越狱后去了那
Where the westerners went when they made their escape.
我在办假证的窝点碰到了他们中的一个
I ran into one at the Forger's Den.
我可以帮忙
I can help.
你觉得就凭你这一只眼睛
And how do you expect to find the foreigners
怎么找到那些外国人
with only one eye?
他们来了  ISIL的人来了
They're here. ISIL are here!
快走  快走  我有个主意
Come on, come on. I have an idea.
那个飞行员
The pilot.
好  跟上我  跟上我
Okay, follow me. Follow me!
别跟丢了他  别跟丢了那飞行员
Don't lose him. Don't lose the pilot.
快走  快  快
Come on. Come on, come on.
乘务员通道  禁止入内
快  快  快
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
不  蹲下走
No, just stay down.
好了  在这里等着
Okay. Wait here.
-什么  -我会回来的
- What? - ‭I'll be back.
-本杰明  -我一个人去
- Benjamin... - I'm going alone.
别去
Don't do it.
停下
Halt!
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
跪下  别动
On your knees! Halt!
出来  出来
Come out. Come out.
你是谁  出示证件
Who are you? Papers.
-别开枪  别开枪  -证件
- Don't shoot. Don't shoot. - ‭Papers.
异教徒
Infidels!
那些异教徒在机场
The infidels are in the airport.
杀害拉马尔的凶手  我亲眼看到的
The killers of Ramal! I've seen them with my own eyes.
-什么  -给我悬赏金
- What? - I want my reward.
一千万里亚尔  我要发财了
The ten million rial. I will be rich.
-带我们去  -你得先保证
- Take us to them. - Not until you promise
我能拿到我的一千万里亚尔
I will get my ten million rial.
如果你说的是实话  钱就归你
If you speak the truth, you'll have the money.
你作为模范穆斯林  动粗的情况有点多啊
You kick a lot of ass for a good Muslim.
你可以把人从街上除掉
You can take the man out of the streets,
但是街上不可能没有一个人
but you can't take the streets out of the man.
你们为什么帮我  你们是谁
Why do you help me? Who are you?
我和你一样
I'm a man, just like you,
都想远离这场混乱
trying to get out of this madness,
但我们无法通过那些大门
but we're not gonna get out through those gates.
现在逃离的唯一办法就是坐飞机  兄弟
The only way out now is up, brother.
747没法起飞
The 747 is done.
有叛军把守
It's been secured by the rebels.
我不是说也门航空
I'm not talking about Yemenia Air.
我说的是那一架飞机
I have my eyes on a different set of wings.
妈妈
Mom?
莎拉
Sara!
你吓了我们一跳
You scared us.
-抱歉  -一切还好吗
- Sorry. - ‭Is everything all right?
挺好的  只是今天过得有点乱
Yeah, no, It's fine. I just-- it's been a crazy day,
我还忘记了迈克的西班牙语课
made more so by the fact that I forgot Mike's Spanish lesson.
-西班牙课  -对啊
- Spanish? - Yeah.
-那不是今天上  -我们车上细说好吗
- That's not today. - We're gonna talk about it in the car, okay?
你确定吗  没事吧
Are you sure? Is everything okay?
是的  我们很好  谢谢
Really. Yes. We're fine. Thank you.
等我把麦克的包给你
Well, let me get Mike's bag.
不了  别管它了  我明天过来拿
No, no, don't worry about it. I'll get it tomorrow.
！支持原创的朋友 一起抵制和鄙视 ‘人人视频   耐卡’这些无耻“盗幕贼”！
■
我要你现在上车
I want you to get in the car
不管发生什么都别出来  好吗
and no matter what you don't get out, okay?
你急着去哪
Where you going so fast?
上车
Get in.
谢谢
Thank you.
昨天系里的会议怎么样了
How was that department meeting yesterday?
你一般都和杀手开会吗
You usually meet with killers?
莎拉  莎拉  别这样  别这样
Sara. Sara. Please, please, please.
让我解释好吗  听我说
I can explain, okay? Just listen to me.
我担心死了
I was sick with worry.
我得保护你  保护我们的家庭
I needed to protect you, to-to protect our family,
我从那家数码店拿了你的手机
so I picked up your phone from the shop
交给了安德鲁·尼尔森
and I took it to Andrew Nelson,
他是我在计算机科学系的一个朋友
my buddy in the computer sciences department.
他做了深入追踪
He did a deep dive,
某种深度数据恢复技术  他成功了
some kind of data archaeology, and he did it.
他追踪到了那些混蛋
He tracked those bastards down.
找到了他们的手机信息
Got their cell information.
所以  我给他们打了电话
So... so I called them,
想着也许
thinking I could-I could maybe
-能和他们达成协议  -你还打他们电话
- make a-make a deal with them. - You called them.
莎拉
Sara?
莎拉  请听我说
Sara, please, listen to me.
莎拉  我这样做是为了你
Sara, this was for you.
你最好现在从我面前滚开
You're gonna want to get out of the way right now.
莎拉  莎拉
Sara. Sara!
萨那火车站
就是这里
This is it.
我们离开这个国家的方法
Our ticket out of the country.
我告诉你  迈克尔  这是个坏主意
I'm telling you, Michael, this is a bad idea.
ISIL组织无处不在
ISIL are everywhere.
不  我们能行
No, I can do this.
你真的花了一千万里亚尔[4万美元]
You really paid the equivalent of ten million rial
买某人的骨灰吗
for some dude's ashes?
不是普通人的骨灰  兄弟
Not just any ashes, man.
是佛莱迪·摩克瑞的骨灰
Freddie Mercury's ashes.
花两倍的钱我都愿意买
I would've paid twice that.
来吧
Come on.
把头低下
Keep your head down.
我们现在该认清现实  往机场走了吧
I think it's time we get sane and head to the airport.
不  不  不
No, no, no.
这里更好  他们控制着火车站
This is better. They control the station.
他们不会猜到我们就在眼皮底下
They'll never think to look for us here now.
他们在利用这里改运货物  而非乘客
They're repurposing those trains for cargo, not passengers.
只要我们上了火车
Once we're on, it's...
我们就能一路向北
it's a straight shot to the north.
他们不会再检查车厢
They won't check the cars again.
这是你看到火车时所想到的吗
That's what you see when you see the train?
我只看到一群人拿着AK47步枪
I see a bunch of dudes with AK-47s
不像我们赤手空拳
who don't look a thing like us.
你真的相信我们能活着登上火车
You really believe we can survive 300 miles on a train
穿过483公里的ISIL组织领地吗
through ISIL territory?
这是自杀
Now that's suicide.
-是挺危险的  -没有开玩笑
- It does seem risky. - No kidding.
不  不
No, no.
我们混进搬运工的队伍  始终低着头
We get in that line of cargo carriers. Keep our heads down.
一旦上了火车  一路上低调行事
Once we're on the train, lay low the rest of the trip.
另外  我们不需要扮得像他们一样
Besides, we don't need to look like them.
"告诉信徒们"
"Tell the believing men
"不要抬头  保持谦逊"
to lower their gaze and be modest."
走
Come on.
刚才那几句都出自《古兰经》[伊斯兰教的最高经典]
From the Koran.
所有路都被封锁了
All the roads are blocked.
所以你得另寻一条去边境的路
So you'll have to find a different way to the border.
搭火车
By train!
海瑟  现在怎么办
Heather, what now?
现在怎么办
What now?
我是说  这一切都是谎言  不是吗
I mean, it was all a lie, wasn't it?
所有事情  我们的生活  婚姻
Everything. Our whole life, our whole marriage.
他和那个朝他开枪的女人聊天时的距离
He was standing as close as you were to me right now,
也不过就像你我现在的距离一样
and he was chatting with the woman who shot him.
你是想说  他一手策划了自己被枪击
You're saying he planned to get himself shot
就像某种变态的表演吗
like it was some sort of, uh, sick performance?
我不知道  我不知道
I don't know. I don't know.
我是说  我...
I mean, I...
-对  他就是在演戏  -但他差点死了
- Yes. Yes, it was. - But he almost died.
所以原计划只是轻伤他的手脚  对吧
So, the plan was to wing him, right?
帮他排除嫌疑  但枪击过了火
To just put him above suspicion, but the shot went wide.
他受了重伤
He gets hit.
-他知道他老婆是医生  -莎拉  别说了
- He knows that he's married to a doctor. - Sara, Sara, stop. Stop.
你三天没睡了  对吗
You haven't slept in three days, right?
你为持械入室的事感到不安
You're upset about the home invasion
你还因为你的爱人
and you're tying yourself up in knots
孩子的生父  可能还活着
because the love of your life,
而让自己操透了心
the father of your baby, might be alive.
而且我联系不上林肯
And I can't get through to Lincoln.
但我看了那段视频
But I saw that video.
绝对是他
It's him.
-好吧  我...  -那就是迈克尔
- Okay, and I... - That's Michael.
我相信你  真的
And I believe you. I do.
-那很重要  -那是最重要的
- And that matters. - That's all that matters.
不  我知道
No, I know.
但雅各布是个好男人
But Jacob is a good man.
他是你丈夫
He's your husband.
-对  -他帮你开启了新的人生
- Yeah. - And he helped you start a new life.
携手同心
Together.
雅各布・奈斯
是他打来的
And that's him.
-我得去接  -不不不  别接
- I have to answer it. ‭- No. No. No, you don't.
有事请留言  会给您回电
Leave a message and we'll get back.
海瑟  海瑟  莎拉在你那吗
Heather, Heather? Is Sara there?
拜托  我需要和她谈谈
Please, I-I need to speak with her.
听着  这里有个天大的误会
Look, there's been a huge misunderstanding
我会把所有事情都解释清楚
and I can explain everything.
你能告诉她吗
Will you just-- will you tell her that?
然后给我回个电话
And to call me?
他在跟踪我
He's tracking me.
莎拉  亲爱的  我是你的闺蜜
Sara, honey. I'm your best friend.
他自然会先给我这打电话
Of-of course he's gonna call here first.
这不能表明他是内奸
It doesn't make him Deep Throat.
不如我们想想有没有更简单的解释
Listen, let's just see if there's a simpler explanation.
好
Okay.
他提到的那个电脑技术人员叫什么名字
What was the name of that computer tech that he mentioned?
安德鲁
Andrew.
尼尔森  安德鲁・尼尔森
Nelson. Andrew Nelson.
好  我在那个系里有个老朋友
Okay, well, I have an old friend in that department.
只要一个电话就能查明雅各布有没有说谎
We can find out if Jacob's full of it in one call.
好的
Okay.
萨那
你
这些靴子应该捐给ISIL的"伟业"
脱下来
把它们放这
这是他仅有的靴子了
关老子屁事
他有话可以自己回答
去火车另一边
Get on the other side of that train!
快  快  快
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on!
快  我们走
Come on, let's go.
你想干什么
What do you want?
看我刚给你发的照片
Look at the picture I just sent you.
凶手就在我的视野范围内
I can see the murderers now.
哪里
Where?
先不告诉你
Not so fast.
带上你的武器  我会盯着他们
Bring your weapons, I will stay on them.
现在老子说了算
And I call the shots now.
检查过了  燃料足够支撑我们离开也门
We checked. There's enough fuel to get us out of Yemen.
问题是  你会开这种老式飞机吗
Question is, can you fly an old bird like this?
试试就知道了
We'll find out.
在萨那城外48公里有另一个车站
There's another station, 30 miles outside Sana'a.
我们可以在那试试  跳上一列火车
We can find a way there, hop a train.
他们不会料到我们会走那个方向
They won't anticipate us coming that way.
在一个必输的赌局中加倍
Doubling down on a bad bet.
就像你七年前与中情局的交易一样
Just like you did seven years back with the CIA.
看看你周围的人
Look around you.
你的计划影响到其他人  而你却看不见
Your plans affect people, you don't even see it.
我不怪你恨我
I don't blame you for resenting me.
你还真说对了  我恨你
You're damn right I resent you.
我明白  林肯  我明白
I see it, Linc. I see it.
每一天  每一秒
Every second of every day,
那些间接受害者
the people, the collateral damage,
那些被我影响的人
the lives I've... affected.
但我不能有那些顾虑
But I can't start thinking about that.
因为如果那样  一切都会完结
Because if I do, then it all falls apart
我们谁也回不了家
and none of us get to go home.
我必须集中注意  深谋远虑
I have to stay focused, be the man with the plan.
就像当年在福克斯河监狱一样
Just like Fox River.
还记得吗
‭Remember?
我们有车了
We got wheels.
好样的
Good work.
只能从机场走
The airport's the only play.
我们离机场8公里
The airport is five miles away.
离边境有好几百公里
The border is hundreds.
听着  机场或许是正确的选择
Look, the airport might be the right choice,
但我相信我的直觉
but I trust my instincts.
凭借直觉让我们活到现在
They've gotten us this far.
直觉告诉我仍然可以从北边突破
And my gut says we can still make it out through the north.
你们自己做决定
Choice is yours.
伙计  虽然我对你一无所知
Look, man, I agree with you,
但我同意你的想法  但是...
even if I don't know you from Adam. But...
既然都跟着他到这里了  所以...
got to go with the horse that got you here, you know? So...
我就跟着他了
he's my horse.
他是我见过最疯狂的人
Craziest horse I've ever met.
但也幸亏有他  才让我们活到现在
But got us this far.
只有不让你送命的疯狂才有用
Crazy only works if it doesn't get you killed.
纽约州
伊萨卡大学
安德鲁吗
Andrew?
海登教授说我们可以找你聊聊
Professor Hayden told us to speak with you?
没错  是的
Oh, yeah. Uh, yeah, right.
不好意思
Sorry.
你好  安德鲁  我是莎拉·斯科菲尔德
Hi, Andrew. I'm Sara Scofield.
谢谢你愿意花时间见我
Thanks for taking the time.
不知道是不是真的
By any chance,
我丈夫雅各布·奈斯有没有让你查我的手机
did my husband Jacob Ness ask you to work on my cell phone?
是的  他有这么做  昨天吧
Yeah, he did, uh, yesterday.
他让你...
What did he, uh--
他让你做了什么
what did he ask you to do?
他说他想找出跟踪他妻子那些人的
He said he was looking to find the contact information
联络信息
for the people who were stalking his wife.
我做了深度数据追踪  把我能找到的给了他
So I did a data dive and gave him what I could find.
怎么做的
How?
他们黑进了你的手机  提取了数据
They hacked your phone and lifted the data,
但过程中留下了蛛丝马迹[电子特征码]
but in the process, left a very slight electronic signature
我能通过它顺藤摸瓜追踪到他们
that I was able to track back to them.
等等  "他们"是谁
Wait, who are "They"?
不知道  是个假的IP地址
Don't know. It was a dummy IP address,
但手机和位置是正确的
but the cell and location were correct.
这些逃不过我的眼睛
They couldn't hide that from me.
你老公打来的
The man himself.
喂
Hello.
莎拉  听我说  我知道你很烦恼
Sara, listen, I know you're upset,
但我需要你来一趟惠特尼海特警局
but I need you to come to the Whitney Heights police station,
马上过来
right now.
拜托了
Please.
现在我们有时间聊聊了
So, now we got some time to talk.
你的名字叫迈克尔
Well, your name's Michael.
！‘人人视频   耐卡’的父母教过你们尊重他人劳动果实 不能不劳而获吧 他们为你羞不羞！？
■
不错
Cool.
你有个哥哥
You have a brother.
还有什么是我不知道的
What else don't I know?
真的  我得知道  长久以来  我这一路上
Serious, I need to know. I've been traveling so fast,
走得太匆忙  都没停下来想想你到底是谁
for so long, I didn't even stop to think who you really are
或我们到底在干什么
or what we're real doing here.
我甚至不知道  你为什么把我卷进这一切
I don't even know why you dragged me into all this, you know?
你得把过去  把细节都忘了  维普
You got to forget the past, Whip, the details.
那些现在都不重要了
None of that matters now.
这么多年来  我是怎么做的
What have my actions been all these years?
是谁一直事无钜细地照顾你
Who's been taking care of you through everything, huh?
是我  对吧
Me. Right?
对吧
Right?
对
Yeah.
一切都不曾改变
Nothing changes.
你依旧是我的得力干将
You're still my whip hand...
得力干将  我是你的得力干将嘛
Whip hand, yeah, I know, I'm your whip hand.
这招已经不好使了  兄弟
It's-- it's not good enough this time, man.
咱能直接打开天窗说亮话吗
Can you just give it to me straight?
我不是小孩子了  我能承受
You know, I'm a big boy, I can handle it.
你是我的得力干将是有原因的
There's a reason you're my whip hand.
一个能改变你一生的原因
A reason that's gonna change your life.
你一定会迎来"柳暗花明又一村"的那一刻
There's a light at the end of the tunnel for you.
搞什么鬼
What the hell was that?
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
赶紧跑
We got to go.
快走
Let's go!
没有出去的路
There's no way out. ‭
医院后面已被炸了个粉碎  通道全堵了
Back of the hospital's been shelled to rubble. It's blocked.
楼上也堵了
Upstairs is blocked, too.
我们去下面
We're gonna go downstairs.
找找出路
Look for a way out.
咱们分头找
You do the same.
惠特尼海特警局
谢谢
Thanks.
怎么回事
What's going on?
莎拉
Sara, just...
跟我们来
just come with us.
你会明白的  拜托
You'll see. Please.
女士您好  是莎拉·斯科菲尔德吗
Hello, ma'am. Sara Scofield?
是我
Yes, sir.
感谢您能来  我是凯南警探
Thanks for coming in, I'm Detective Kennan.
我们希望您能指认谁闯入了您家
We'd like you to point out who broke into your home.
还有
And...
朝您丈夫开枪的人
the one who shot your husband.
3号和4号
It's three and four.
那一男一女就是枪手
The man and the woman was the shooter.
确定吗
Are you sure?
是的
Yes, sir.
百分百确定
Yes, I'm absolutely sure.
肯定会有出路
There's got to be a way out.
肯定有和路面相连的地方
Something-- something that connects to the surface.
往下找没用的  迈克尔
Going down's not gonna work, Michael.
我们得搞好埋伏  准备反击
We need to set up an ambush and fight.
是啊  武力永远是你的默认选择
Yeah, well, fighting is your default setting.
可拳头无法解决一切
It's not always about fists.
我说过了  没有出路
I'm telling you, there's no way out.
那就找个能打的玩意儿  傻瓜
Then find something to fight with, you idiot.
现在可不是玩这些"情趣游戏"的时候
I don't think it's that kind of a party,
但我喜欢你的品位
but I like your style.
你拿这个准备做什么
What are you going to do with that?
不知道
I don't know.
总比赤手空拳好
Beats a fist.
医用酒精
Rubbing alcohol?
你他妈想干嘛
What the hell are you doing?
你会瞎的  蠢货
You'll go blind, you idiot.
纯度才95%
It's only 95% alcohol.
我还不至于全瞎
I'll only go 95% blind.
那里  那有个通风井
There. There's an air shaft.
现在该武力登场了
Well, it's about fists now.
迈克尔
Michael?
不  是他们
No. It's them.
我的第一个恋人比我大很多
My first lover was much older than me.
他是我朋友的父亲
He was my friend's father.
他叫马西
Massi was his name.
这在当时是不为人知的
It was the greatest of scandals
最大的丑闻
that we kept to ourselves.
后来却被他妻子发现了
But his wife discovered us
告诉了她的兄弟们
and told her brothers.
马西被带到沙漠里
Massi was taken into the desert...
埋掉了
and buried.
是活埋
Alive.
他们用破布包着他的眼睛给了我
They brought his eyes to me in a rag.
我要你用那个杀了我
I need you to use that on me.
结束我的痛苦
End my suffering.
什么  这个吗
What, this?
雅说得对
Ja's right.
这种逃亡毫无意义
All this running is pointless.
你知道他们会在这怎么折磨我吗
Do you know what they will do to me here,
远不止挖眼这么简单
away from seeing eyes?
我不能
I can't.
我不会让那种事发生
I won't let that happen.
你明白吗
Do you understand?
我不会让它发生的
I won't let that happen.
听着  希德
Listen. Sid.
我不会放弃
I'm not giving up.
不管是不是同性恋  你也不能放弃
And queer or no, you're not, either.
他们才是错的
They're in the wrong.
不是你
Not you.
你要用那个干嘛
What are you gonna do with that?
*我已付出代价*
*I've paid my dues*
*一次又一次*
*Time after time*
*我已认罪服刑*
*I've served my sentence*
*却从未犯下罪行*
*But committed no crime...*
迈克尔  快点
Michael, come on.
对不起  哥
I'm sorry, Linc.
我那时本该来找你的
I should have come to you.
波塞冬跟我交易的时候
I should've asked for your help
我就该去找你帮忙的  是我搞砸了
when Poseidon offered me the deal. I blew it.
那个时候  我想的是
At the time, I thought,
如果我自己来应对
if I dealt with it myself,
那痛苦只会留给我
the pain would only be mine.
但恰恰相反  我打开了潘多拉的盒子
But instead I opened this Pandora's Box.
我本想让情况变好
I wanted to make it better,
但我只是让每个人的处境都变得更糟
but I only made it worse for everyone.
在这过程中
And somewhere in there...
我成了一个幽灵
became a ghost.
我犯了很多错误
I made a lot of mistakes.
做了很多不明智不完美的选择
A lot of foolish, imperfect choices,
但所有这些...
but every one of them...
我做的所有这些都是出于爱
every one of them I made for love.
我知道  我知道
I know. I know.
迈克尔
Michael,
你是我认识的最聪明的人
you're the smartest person I've ever known,
但你不能把所有担子都由自己来扛
but you can't carry the load on your shoulders alone.
你需要有人分担这些负担
You need to share the burden.
对
Yes.
这才是一家人
That's family.
这才是家人该做的
That's what family's for.
莎拉  我不知道你怎么想的  但是...
Sara, I don't know what you thought, but...
我只是一个担心妻子的丈夫而已
I'm just a husband who was worried about his wife.
没错  我本该早告诉你我做的事  但...
And yeah, I-I should have told you what I was doing, but...
我感觉...
Look, I felt like...
一切都失控了
like everything was spiraling out of control
而我必须尽我所能去保护你
and I had to do whatever I could to protect you.
所以你觉得你该去跟两个职业杀手联系
So you thought you'd contact two hired killers?
我是想去扮演救星的角色
I was trying to play the white knight.
扮得并不好
Not very well.
这的确是疯了
And it was insanity.
我被吓坏了
I was scared to death.
我就是个哭鼻子的笨蛋
A-A blubbering idiot,
我想他们可以用钱收买  知道吗
but I thought they would respond to money, you know?
无论给多少钱都行  只要能让他们放手
Pay them whatever it took to make them go away.
比他们拿到手的还要多
More than they were already making:
五万美元
$50,000.
听我说  我...
Look, I, uh...
我在里面放了追踪器  莎拉
I had a tracker in it, Sara.
这个小东西
This little thing,
但他们没有碰它
but they didn't touch it.
我在碰面前就联系了警察
I contacted the police before the meet,
不管怎样我们抓到他们了
but we nailed them anyhow.
我们抓到他们了
We nailed them.
雅各布
Jacob.
我很抱歉让你经历了这些
I am so sorry I put you through this.
我们上吧
Let's do this.
扳手加管子来对抗AK步枪
A wrench and a pipe against AKs.
会很有趣的
It'll be fun.
我一直都想狠狠地痛扁这帮混蛋一顿
I've always wanted a crack at these bastards.
*我已付出代价*
*I paid my dues*
*一次又一次*
*Time after time*
！尊重原创  远离“盗幕贼”！笑看‘人人视频   耐卡’ 寄生虫们能走多远 ！
■
*我已认罪服刑*
*I've served my sentence*
回来
Come back.
*却从未犯下罪行*
*But committed no crime*
*严重的错误*
*And bad mistakes*
快过来
Get over here...
*我也犯过一些*
*I've made a few*
你会把自己害死的
You're gonna get yourself killed!
*我是自作自受*
*I've had my share of sand kicked in my face*
*但我熬过来了*
*But I've come through*
*我就这么一直前行*
*And I go on and on and on*
*我们是冠军*
*We are the champions*
*我的朋友们*
*My friends*
*我们是冠军*
*We are the champions*
爱死你了  你这个日本疯子  太牛了
I love you, you crazy Japanese son of a bitch!
我是韩国人  哥们
It's Korean, champ.
无所谓啦  我还是爱你
Whatever. I still love you.
ISIL的人就像蟑螂
ISIL are like roaches.
很快就会涌来更多
More will be here soon.
怎么办
What do we do now?
让我喘口气想想再做决定
I need to take a break from making decisions.
林肯  要不机场吧
Linc, airport?
就机场
Airport.
有个人你得联系一下
I got someone I want you to talk to.
伙计
Oh, man!
我真没想到这辈子还能再听到你的声音
Now that's a voice I never thought I'd hear again.
你可得好好跟我解释解释了  伙计
Man, you got some explaining to do, brother,
-居然搞出复活的套路  -很快就会的
- risen from the dead and all. - Soon.
去哪里找你
Where can we meet you?
2号飞机库  正对着跑道
Hangar two. Right off the main runway.
但你们最好快点
But you better hurry your ass up.
2号飞机库对吗
Hangar two?
我们能在20分钟后赶到
We could be there in 20 minutes.
We can be there in 20 minutes.
不知道我们能不能撑这么久
I don't know if we have that long.
等我们  我们一定到
Wait for us. We'll be there.
得走了
We got to move.
希德
Sid...
Sid!
我听到了你们打的电话  异教徒
I heard your call, infidel.
你们就算"插翅"也难飞[坐飞机]
Wings will not carry you to safety.
只要老子一个电话
One call,
我的兄弟们就会在机场找到你们的朋友们
and my brothers will find your friends at the airport.
找到那帮异教徒了
其他人在哪我也知道了
-希德  -希德
- Sid! - Sid!
狗娘养的东西
Son of a bitch.
不  不  不
No, no, no, no, no.
说话  希德  坚持住
Talk to me, Sid. Stay with us.
坚持住
Stay with us.
希德
Sid...
Sid.
他死了
He's gone.
别在这人渣身上浪费力气
Don't waste yourself on him.
活下去就是赢了他
You'll beat him by surviving.
你们都会死  听到了吗
You will die, you hear me?
你们都会死光光
You will all die!
他们正调集更多的卡车就位
They're moving more trucks into position.
不能再等了
‭We can't wait.
待会儿跑道长度就不够起飞了
There won't be enough runway to take off.
我们必须走了
We must go now.
我欠林肯一条命  我不能抛弃他
I owe Lincoln my life. He deserves better.
但这么多人的性命安危全在我们手中
But with so many souls in our hands,
我们真的有选择吗
do we really have a choice?
听着  我们再等五分钟  好吗
Listen, we wait five more minutes. Okay?
之后就只能救一个是一个了
And then we take care of the souls that we can.
明白了吗
Understand?
你干什么呢
What the hell are you doing?
你干什么
The hell are you doing?
听着  我们不能丢下我朋友
Listen, we are not leaving my friends!
关掉  关掉它
Shut it down. Shut it down!
你会把我们都害死的
You would condemn us all to death.
你阻止我  谁都跑不了
If you stop me, no one gets out.
你朋友们还能跑得了  我们不行
Your friends can still make it to safety. We will not.
喂
Yeah?
钞票哥  你们得赶紧走了  伙计
C-Note? You got to get out of here, man.
不  不  不
Hey, no, no, no, no.
我们能做到的  一定能
W-We can do this thing, man. We can do it.
不  赶紧走  否则你和孩子们都得死
No! Go now! Otherwise, you and the kids are dead!
■
微信扫瞄
上方二维码
关注TV哔
一起哔哔哔
m 350 100 l 350 110 l 360 110 l 360 100 m 360 100 m 100 320 l 100 330 l 110 330 l 110 320 m 110 320 m 260 230 l 260 240 l 270 240 l 270 230 m 270 230 m 220 230 l 220 240 l 230 240 l 230 230 m 230 230 m 270 300 l 270 310 l 280 310 l 280 300 m 280 300 m 360 60 l 360 70 l 370 70 l 370 60 m 370 60 m 130 40 l 130 50 l 140 50 l 140 40 m 140 40 m 180 350 l 180 360 l 190 360 l 190 350 m 190 350 m 190 340 l 190 350 l 200 350 l 200 340 m 200 340 m 150 260 l 150 270 l 160 270 l 160 260 m 160 260 m 40 210 l 40 220 l 50 220 l 50 210 m 50 210 m 180 50 l 180 60 l 190 60 l 190 50 m 190 50 m 160 210 l 160 220 l 170 220 l 170 210 m 170 210 m 290 190 l 290 200 l 300 200 l 300 190 m 300 190 m 170 240 l 170 250 l 180 250 l 180 240 m 180 240 m 300 160 l 300 170 l 310 170 l 310 160 m 310 160 m 330 210 l 330 220 l 340 220 l 340 210 m 340 210 m 70 60 l 70 70 l 80 70 l 80 60 m 80 60 m 340 180 l 340 190 l 350 190 l 350 180 m 350 180 m 320 140 l 320 150 l 330 150 l 330 140 m 330 140 m 90 280 l 90 290 l 100 290 l 100 280 m 100 280 m 330 150 l 330 160 l 340 160 l 340 150 m 340 150 m 240 180 l 240 190 l 250 190 l 250 180 m 250 180 m 220 140 l 220 150 l 230 150 l 230 140 m 230 140 m 270 230 l 270 240 l 280 240 l 280 230 m 280 230 m 250 190 l 250 200 l 260 200 l 260 190 m 260 190 m 260 160 l 260 170 l 270 170 l 270 160 m 270 160 m 130 130 l 130 140 l 140 140 l 140 130 m 140 130 m 270 130 l 270 140 l 280 140 l 280 130 m 280 130 m 140 180 l 140 190 l 150 190 l 150 180 m 150 180 m 150 190 l 150 200 l 160 200 l 160 190 m 160 190 m 130 230 l 130 240 l 140 240 l 140 230 m 140 230 m 280 250 l 280 260 l 290 260 l 290 250 m 290 250 m 160 120 l 160 130 l 170 130 l 170 120 m 170 120 m 290 200 l 290 210 l 300 210 l 300 200 m 300 200 m 310 100 l 310 110 l 320 110 l 320 100 m 320 100 m 60 160 l 60 170 l 70 170 l 70 160 m 70 160 m 330 80 l 330 90 l 340 90 l 340 80 m 340 80 m 70 210 l 70 220 l 80 220 l 80 210 m 80 210 m 200 110 l 200 120 l 210 120 l 210 110 m 210 110 m 100 180 l 100 190 l 110 190 l 110 180 m 110 180 m 340 310 l 340 320 l 350 320 l 350 310 m 350 310 m 110 190 l 110 200 l 120 200 l 120 190 m 120 190 m 240 250 l 240 260 l 250 260 l 250 250 m 250 250 m 200 330 l 200 340 l 210 340 l 210 330 m 210 330 m 100 360 l 100 370 l 110 370 l 110 360 m 110 360 m 250 120 l 250 130 l 260 130 l 260 120 m 260 120 m 210 280 l 210 290 l 220 290 l 220 280 m 220 280 m 140 130 l 140 140 l 150 140 l 150 130 m 150 130 m 120 290 l 120 300 l 130 300 l 130 290 m 130 290 m 150 80 l 150 90 l 160 90 l 160 80 m 160 80 m 130 240 l 130 250 l 140 250 l 140 240 m 140 240 m 280 320 l 280 330 l 290 330 l 290 320 m 290 320 m 190 140 l 190 150 l 200 150 l 200 140 m 200 140 m 150 300 l 150 310 l 160 310 l 160 300 m 160 300 m 300 340 l 300 350 l 310 350 l 310 340 m 310 340 m 40 90 l 40 100 l 50 100 l 50 90 m 50 90 m 280 60 l 280 70 l 290 70 l 290 60 m 290 60 m 160 330 l 160 340 l 170 340 l 170 330 m 170 330 m 50 40 l 50 50 l 60 50 l 60 40 m 60 40 m 80 150 l 80 160 l 90 160 l 90 150 m 90 150 m 320 280 l 320 290 l 330 290 l 330 280 m 330 280 m 90 140 l 90 150 l 100 150 l 100 140 m 100 140 m 330 330 l 330 340 l 340 340 l 340 330 m 340 330 m 100 50 l 100 60 l 110 60 l 110 50 m 110 50 m 340 60 l 340 70 l 350 70 l 350 60 m 350 60 m 80 210 l 80 220 l 90 220 l 90 210 m 90 210 m 230 310 l 230 320 l 240 320 l 240 310 m 240 310 m 350 310 l 350 320 l 360 320 l 360 310 m 360 310 m 200 240 l 200 250 l 210 250 l 210 240 m 210 240 m 100 310 l 100 320 l 110 320 l 110 310 m 110 310 m 360 270 l 360 280 l 370 280 l 370 270 m 370 270 m 260 340 l 260 350 l 270 350 l 270 340 m 270 340 m 220 260 l 220 270 l 230 270 l 230 260 m 230 260 m 120 40 l 120 50 l 130 50 l 130 40 m 130 40 m 140 300 l 140 310 l 150 310 l 150 300 m 150 300 m 40 320 l 40 330 l 50 330 l 50 320 m 50 320 m 160 240 l 160 250 l 170 250 l 170 240 m 170 240 m 310 240 l 310 250 l 320 250 l 320 240 m 320 240 m 170 290 l 170 300 l 180 300 l 180 290 m 180 290 m 60 340 l 60 350 l 70 350 l 70 340 m 70 340 m 300 70 l 300 80 l 310 80 l 310 70 m 310 70 m 310 140 l 310 150 l 320 150 l 320 140 m 320 140 m 80 280 l 80 290 l 90 290 l 90 280 m 90 280 m 230 360 l 230 370 l 240 370 l 240 360 m 240 360 m 350 40 l 350 50 l 360 50 l 360 40 m 360 40 m 200 150 l 200 160 l 210 160 l 210 150 m 210 150 m 100 220 l 100 230 l 110 230 l 110 220 m 110 220 m 250 300 l 250 310 l 260 310 l 260 300 m 260 300 m 270 240 l 270 250 l 280 250 l 280 240 m 280 240 m 250 80 l 250 90 l 260 90 l 260 80 m 260 80 m 120 110 l 120 120 l 130 120 l 130 110 m 130 110 m 360 80 l 360 90 l 370 90 l 370 80 m 370 80 m 260 150 l 260 160 l 270 160 l 270 150 m 270 150 m 180 110 l 180 120 l 190 120 l 190 110 m 190 110 m 50 220 l 50 230 l 60 230 l 60 220 m 60 220 m 290 170 l 290 180 l 300 180 l 300 170 m 300 170 m 170 220 l 170 230 l 180 230 l 180 220 m 180 220 m 70 80 l 70 90 l 80 90 l 80 80 m 80 80 m 320 80 l 320 90 l 330 90 l 330 80 m 330 80 m 350 130 l 350 140 l 360 140 l 360 130 m 360 130 m 90 100 l 90 110 l 100 110 l 100 100 m 100 100 m 330 130 l 330 140 l 340 140 l 340 130 m 340 130 m 200 60 l 200 70 l 210 70 l 210 60 m 210 60 m 340 260 l 340 270 l 350 270 l 350 260 m 350 260 m 350 270 l 350 280 l 360 280 l 360 270 m 360 270 m 90 360 l 90 370 l 100 370 l 100 360 m 100 360 m 120 180 l 120 190 l 130 190 l 130 180 m 130 180 m 260 60 l 260 70 l 270 70 l 270 60 m 270 60 m 140 160 l 140 170 l 150 170 l 150 160 m 150 160 m 120 240 l 120 250 l 130 250 l 130 240 m 130 240 m 150 50 l 150 60 l 160 60 l 160 50 m 160 50 m 130 210 l 130 220 l 140 220 l 140 210 m 140 210 m 280 270 l 280 280 l 290 280 l 290 270 m 290 270 m 180 180 l 180 190 l 190 190 l 190 180 m 190 180 m 290 260 l 290 270 l 300 270 l 300 260 m 300 260 m 190 190 l 190 200 l 200 200 l 200 190 m 200 190 m 40 40 l 40 50 l 50 50 l 50 40 m 50 40 m 70 170 l 70 180 l 80 180 l 80 170 m 80 170 m 310 280 l 310 290 l 320 290 l 320 280 m 320 280 m 50 170 l 50 180 l 60 180 l 60 170 m 60 170 m 320 70 l 320 80 l 330 80 l 330 70 m 330 70 m 60 140 l 60 150 l 70 150 l 70 140 m 70 140 m 330 60 l 330 70 l 340 70 l 340 60 m 340 60 m 100 160 l 100 170 l 110 170 l 110 160 m 110 160 m 210 80 l 210 90 l 220 90 l 220 80 m 220 80 m 240 270 l 240 280 l 250 280 l 250 270 m 250 270 m 220 70 l 220 80 l 230 80 l 230 70 m 230 70 m 150 360 l 150 370 l 160 370 l 160 360 m 160 360 m 270 40 l 270 50 l 280 50 l 280 40 m 280 40 m 120 310 l 120 320 l 130 320 l 130 310 m 130 310 m 360 120 l 360 130 l 370 130 l 370 120 m 370 120 m 140 210 l 140 220 l 150 220 l 150 210 m 150 210 m 290 350 l 290 360 l 300 360 l 300 350 m 300 350 m 300 320 l 300 330 l 310 330 l 310 320 m 310 320 m 50 100 l 50 110 l 60 110 l 60 100 m 60 100 m 320 300 l 320 310 l 330 310 l 330 300 m 330 300 m 300 100 l 300 110 l 310 110 l 310 100 m 310 100 m 90 120 l 90 130 l 100 130 l 100 120 m 100 120 m 70 280 l 70 290 l 80 290 l 80 280 m 80 280 m 340 40 l 340 50 l 350 50 l 350 40 m 350 40 m 230 330 l 230 340 l 240 340 l 240 330 m 240 330 m 300 360 l 300 370 l 310 370 l 310 360 m 310 360 m 90 220 l 90 230 l 100 230 l 100 220 m 100 220 m 240 340 l 240 350 l 250 350 l 250 340 m 250 340 m 230 70 l 230 80 l 240 80 l 240 70 m 240 70 m 260 320 l 260 330 l 270 330 l 270 320 m 270 320 m 130 70 l 130 80 l 140 80 l 140 70 m 140 70 m 140 280 l 140 290 l 150 290 l 150 280 m 150 280 m 40 340 l 40 350 l 50 350 l 50 340 m 50 340 m 180 60 l 180 70 l 190 70 l 190 60 m 190 60 m 160 260 l 160 270 l 170 270 l 170 260 m 170 260 m 320 210 l 320 220 l 330 220 l 330 210 m 330 210 m 60 320 l 60 330 l 70 330 l 70 320 m 70 320 m 300 50 l 300 60 l 310 60 l 310 50 m 310 50 m 330 240 l 330 250 l 340 250 l 340 240 m 340 240 m 80 300 l 80 310 l 90 310 l 90 300 m 90 300 m 330 180 l 330 190 l 340 190 l 340 180 m 340 180 m 100 200 l 100 210 l 110 210 l 110 200 m 110 200 m 80 360 l 80 370 l 90 370 l 90 360 m 90 360 m 210 120 l 210 130 l 220 130 l 220 120 m 220 120 m 270 260 l 270 270 l 280 270 l 280 260 m 280 260 m 120 130 l 120 140 l 130 140 l 130 130 m 130 130 m 360 100 l 360 110 l 370 110 l 370 100 m 370 100 m 260 130 l 260 140 l 270 140 l 270 130 m 270 130 m 130 80 l 130 90 l 140 90 l 140 80 m 140 80 m 270 160 l 270 170 l 280 170 l 280 160 m 280 160 m 150 140 l 150 150 l 160 150 l 160 140 m 160 140 m 40 250 l 40 260 l 50 260 l 50 250 m 50 250 m 280 220 l 280 230 l 290 230 l 290 220 m 290 220 m 180 90 l 180 100 l 190 100 l 190 90 m 190 90 m 160 170 l 160 180 l 170 180 l 170 170 m 170 170 m 50 200 l 50 210 l 60 210 l 60 200 m 60 200 m 290 230 l 290 240 l 300 240 l 300 230 m 300 230 m 300 120 l 300 130 l 310 130 l 310 120 m 310 120 m 70 100 l 70 110 l 80 110 l 80 100 m 80 100 m 50 140 l 50 150 l 60 150 l 60 140 m 60 140 m 320 100 l 320 110 l 330 110 l 330 100 m 330 100 m 350 150 l 350 160 l 360 160 l 360 150 m 360 150 m 200 80 l 200 90 l 210 90 l 210 80 m 210 80 m 340 240 l 340 250 l 350 250 l 350 240 m 350 240 m 210 50 l 210 60 l 220 60 l 220 50 m 220 50 m 350 210 l 350 220 l 360 220 l 360 210 m 360 210 m 220 100 l 220 110 l 230 110 l 230 100 m 230 100 m 200 300 l 200 310 l 210 310 l 210 300 m 210 300 m 250 150 l 250 160 l 260 160 l 260 150 m 260 150 m 140 360 l 140 370 l 150 370 l 150 360 m 150 360 m 210 310 l 210 320 l 220 320 l 220 310 m 220 310 m 130 170 l 130 180 l 140 180 l 140 170 m 140 170 m 220 360 l 220 370 l 230 370 l 230 360 m 230 360 m 270 90 l 270 100 l 280 100 l 280 90 m 280 90 m 140 140 l 140 150 l 150 150 l 150 140 m 150 140 m 150 70 l 150 80 l 160 80 l 160 70 m 160 70 m 280 290 l 280 300 l 290 300 l 290 290 m 290 290 m 180 160 l 180 170 l 190 170 l 190 160 m 190 160 m 160 80 l 160 90 l 170 90 l 170 80 m 170 80 m 140 240 l 140 250 l 150 250 l 150 240 m 150 240 m 170 130 l 170 140 l 180 140 l 180 130 m 180 130 m 150 290 l 150 300 l 160 300 l 160 290 m 160 290 m 300 230 l 300 240 l 310 240 l 310 230 m 310 230 m 40 60 l 40 70 l 50 70 l 50 60 m 50 60 m 70 190 l 70 200 l 80 200 l 80 190 m 80 190 m 60 120 l 60 130 l 70 130 l 70 120 m 70 120 m 330 40 l 330 50 l 340 50 l 340 40 m 340 40 m 290 360 l 290 370 l 300 370 l 300 360 m 300 360 m 100 60 l 100 70 l 110 70 l 110 60 m 110 60 m 340 350 l 340 360 l 350 360 l 350 350 m 350 350 m 80 260 l 80 270 l 90 270 l 90 260 m 90 260 m 230 260 l 230 270 l 240 270 l 240 260 m 240 260 m 110 150 l 110 160 l 120 160 l 120 150 m 120 150 m 240 210 l 240 220 l 250 220 l 250 210 m 250 210 m 200 210 l 200 220 l 210 220 l 210 210 m 210 210 m 210 320 l 210 330 l 220 330 l 220 320 m 220 320 m 360 240 l 360 250 l 370 250 l 370 240 m 370 240 m 220 310 l 220 320 l 230 320 l 230 310 m 230 310 m 270 60 l 270 70 l 280 70 l 280 60 m 280 60 m 120 330 l 120 340 l 130 340 l 130 330 m 130 330 m 180 270 l 180 280 l 190 280 l 190 270 m 190 270 m 190 260 l 190 270 l 200 270 l 200 260 m 200 260 m 170 60 l 170 70 l 180 70 l 180 60 m 180 60 m 300 300 l 300 310 l 310 310 l 310 300 m 310 300 m 280 100 l 280 110 l 290 110 l 290 100 m 290 100 m 160 290 l 160 300 l 170 300 l 170 290 m 170 290 m 310 230 l 310 240 l 320 240 l 320 230 m 320 230 m 170 320 l 170 330 l 180 330 l 180 320 m 180 320 m 320 240 l 320 250 l 330 250 l 330 240 m 330 240 m 60 70 l 60 80 l 70 80 l 70 70 m 70 70 m 300 80 l 300 90 l 310 90 l 310 80 m 310 80 m 330 290 l 330 300 l 340 300 l 340 290 m 340 290 m 70 300 l 70 310 l 80 310 l 80 300 m 80 300 m 100 90 l 100 100 l 110 100 l 110 90 m 110 90 m 340 100 l 340 110 l 350 110 l 350 100 m 350 100 m 80 330 l 80 340 l 90 340 l 90 330 m 90 330 m 70 360 l 70 370 l 80 370 l 80 360 m 80 360 m 100 350 l 100 360 l 110 360 l 110 350 m 110 350 m 250 330 l 250 340 l 260 340 l 260 330 m 260 330 m 240 100 l 240 110 l 250 110 l 250 100 m 250 100 m 220 220 l 220 230 l 230 230 l 230 220 m 230 220 m 270 310 l 270 320 l 280 320 l 280 310 m 280 310 m 360 50 l 360 60 l 370 60 l 370 50 m 370 50 m 180 340 l 180 350 l 190 350 l 190 340 m 190 340 m 140 100 l 140 110 l 150 110 l 150 100 m 150 100 m 280 170 l 280 180 l 290 180 l 290 170 m 290 170 m 160 200 l 160 210 l 170 210 l 170 200 m 170 200 m 190 90 l 190 100 l 200 100 l 200 90 m 200 90 m 170 250 l 170 260 l 180 260 l 180 250 m 180 250 m 320 230 l 320 240 l 330 240 l 330 230 m 330 230 m 60 300 l 60 310 l 70 310 l 70 300 m 70 300 m 300 190 l 300 200 l 310 200 l 310 190 m 310 190 m 70 70 l 70 80 l 80 80 l 80 70 m 80 70 m 340 130 l 340 140 l 350 140 l 350 130 m 350 130 m 80 80 l 80 90 l 90 90 l 90 80 m 90 80 m 330 160 l 330 170 l 340 170 l 340 160 m 340 160 m 100 260 l 100 270 l 110 270 l 110 260 m 110 260 m 210 180 l 210 190 l 220 190 l 220 180 m 220 180 m 110 270 l 110 280 l 120 280 l 120 270 m 120 270 m 260 250 l 260 260 l 270 260 l 270 250 m 270 250 m 240 170 l 240 180 l 250 180 l 250 170 m 250 170 m 130 360 l 130 370 l 140 370 l 140 360 m 140 360 m 250 40 l 250 50 l 260 50 l 260 40 m 260 40 m 210 360 l 210 370 l 220 370 l 220 360 m 220 360 m 360 280 l 360 290 l 370 290 l 370 280 m 370 280 m 260 190 l 260 200 l 270 200 l 270 190 m 270 190 m 130 140 l 130 150 l 140 150 l 140 140 m 140 140 m 270 180 l 270 190 l 280 190 l 280 180 m 280 180 m 140 50 l 140 60 l 150 60 l 150 50 m 150 50 m 280 240 l 280 250 l 290 250 l 290 240 m 290 240 m 160 190 l 160 200 l 170 200 l 170 190 m 170 190 m 290 210 l 290 220 l 300 220 l 300 210 m 300 210 m 60 250 l 60 260 l 70 260 l 70 250 m 70 250 m 300 260 l 300 270 l 310 270 l 310 260 m 310 260 m 40 170 l 40 180 l 50 180 l 50 170 m 50 170 m 70 120 l 70 130 l 80 130 l 80 120 m 80 120 m 80 70 l 80 80 l 90 80 l 90 70 m 90 70 m 320 40 l 320 50 l 330 50 l 330 40 m 330 40 m 200 100 l 200 110 l 210 110 l 210 100 m 210 100 m 230 230 l 230 240 l 240 240 l 240 230 m 240 230 m 210 110 l 210 120 l 220 120 l 220 110 m 220 110 m 350 230 l 350 240 l 360 240 l 360 230 m 360 230 m 220 80 l 220 90 l 230 90 l 230 80 m 230 80 m 200 320 l 200 330 l 210 330 l 210 320 m 210 320 m 360 350 l 360 360 l 370 360 l 370 350 m 370 350 m 260 100 l 260 110 l 270 110 l 270 100 m 270 100 m 220 340 l 220 350 l 230 350 l 230 340 m 230 340 m 270 110 l 270 120 l 280 120 l 280 110 m 280 110 m 140 120 l 140 130 l 150 130 l 150 120 m 150 120 m 150 90 l 150 100 l 160 100 l 160 90 m 160 90 m 280 310 l 280 320 l 290 320 l 290 310 m 290 310 m 160 100 l 160 110 l 170 110 l 170 100 m 170 100 m 140 220 l 140 230 l 150 230 l 150 220 m 150 220 m 300 210 l 300 220 l 310 220 l 310 210 m 310 210 m 40 80 l 40 90 l 50 90 l 50 80 m 50 80 m 160 320 l 160 330 l 170 330 l 170 320 m 170 320 m 310 320 l 310 330 l 320 330 l 320 320 m 320 320 m 320 350 l 320 360 l 330 360 l 330 350 m 330 350 m 60 100 l 60 110 l 70 110 l 70 100 m 70 100 m 100 40 l 100 50 l 110 50 l 110 40 m 110 40 m 80 200 l 80 210 l 90 210 l 90 200 m 90 200 m 230 280 l 230 290 l 240 290 l 240 280 m 240 280 m 60 360 l 60 370 l 70 370 l 70 360 m 70 360 m 100 300 l 100 310 l 110 310 l 110 300 m 110 300 m 250 220 l 250 230 l 260 230 l 260 220 m 260 220 m 360 260 l 360 270 l 370 270 l 370 260 m 370 260 m 220 290 l 220 300 l 230 300 l 230 290 m 230 290 m 270 320 l 270 330 l 280 330 l 280 320 m 280 320 m 180 250 l 180 260 l 190 260 l 190 250 m 190 250 m 140 330 l 140 340 l 150 340 l 150 330 m 150 330 m 150 200 l 150 210 l 160 210 l 160 200 m 160 200 m 300 280 l 300 290 l 310 290 l 310 280 m 310 280 m 40 310 l 40 320 l 50 320 l 50 310 m 50 310 m 160 310 l 160 320 l 170 320 l 170 310 m 170 310 m 310 250 l 310 260 l 320 260 l 320 250 m 320 250 m 50 300 l 50 310 l 60 310 l 60 300 m 60 300 m 170 300 l 170 310 l 180 310 l 180 300 m 180 300 m 300 60 l 300 70 l 310 70 l 310 60 m 310 60 m 330 270 l 330 280 l 340 280 l 340 270 m 340 270 m 70 320 l 70 330 l 80 330 l 80 320 m 80 320 m 310 150 l 310 160 l 320 160 l 320 150 m 320 150 m 340 80 l 340 90 l 350 90 l 350 80 m 350 80 m 240 300 l 240 310 l 250 310 l 250 300 m 250 300 m 200 140 l 200 150 l 210 150 l 210 140 m 210 140 m 100 330 l 100 340 l 110 340 l 110 330 m 110 330 m 230 110 l 230 120 l 240 120 l 240 110 m 240 110 m 210 150 l 210 160 l 220 160 l 220 150 m 220 150 m 120 360 l 120 370 l 130 370 l 130 360 m 130 360 m 260 200 l 260 210 l 270 210 l 270 200 m 270 200 m 240 40 l 240 50 l 250 50 l 250 40 m 250 40 m 220 200 l 220 210 l 230 210 l 230 200 m 230 200 m 250 90 l 250 100 l 260 100 l 260 90 m 260 90 m 120 100 l 120 110 l 130 110 l 130 100 m 130 100 m 360 70 l 360 80 l 370 80 l 370 70 m 370 70 m 260 140 l 260 150 l 270 150 l 270 140 m 270 140 m 140 80 l 140 90 l 150 90 l 150 80 m 150 80 m 190 290 l 190 300 l 200 300 l 200 290 m 200 290 m 40 220 l 40 230 l 50 230 l 50 220 m 50 220 m 280 190 l 280 200 l 290 200 l 290 190 m 290 190 m 180 100 l 180 110 l 190 110 l 190 100 m 190 100 m 190 110 l 190 120 l 200 120 l 200 110 m 200 110 m 170 230 l 170 240 l 180 240 l 180 230 m 180 230 m 60 280 l 60 290 l 70 290 l 70 280 m 70 280 m 300 170 l 300 180 l 310 180 l 310 170 m 310 170 m 40 120 l 40 130 l 50 130 l 50 120 m 50 120 m 310 40 l 310 50 l 320 50 l 320 40 m 320 40 m 340 190 l 340 200 l 350 200 l 350 190 m 350 190 m 80 100 l 80 110 l 90 110 l 90 100 m 90 100 m 330 140 l 330 150 l 340 150 l 340 140 m 340 140 m 100 240 l 100 250 l 110 250 l 110 240 m 110 240 m 230 160 l 230 170 l 240 170 l 240 160 m 240 160 m 110 210 l 110 220 l 120 220 l 120 210 m 120 210 m 360 300 l 360 310 l 370 310 l 370 300 m 370 300 m 130 220 l 130 230 l 140 230 l 140 220 m 140 220 m 50 240 l 50 250 l 60 250 l 60 240 m 60 240 m 190 160 l 190 170 l 200 170 l 200 160 m 200 160 m 60 230 l 60 240 l 70 240 l 70 230 m 70 230 m 300 240 l 300 250 l 310 250 l 310 240 m 310 240 m 50 180 l 50 190 l 60 190 l 60 180 m 60 180 m 80 170 l 80 180 l 90 180 l 90 170 m 90 170 m 320 60 l 320 70 l 330 70 l 330 60 m 330 60 m 60 170 l 60 180 l 70 180 l 70 170 m 70 170 m 90 40 l 90 50 l 100 50 l 100 40 m 100 40 m 330 70 l 330 80 l 340 80 l 340 70 m 340 70 m 50 360 l 50 370 l 60 370 l 60 360 m 60 360 m 340 280 l 340 290 l 350 290 l 350 280 m 350 280 m 210 90 l 210 100 l 220 100 l 220 90 m 220 90 m 110 180 l 110 190 l 120 190 l 120 180 m 120 180 m 240 260 l 240 270 l 250 270 l 250 260 m 250 260 m 220 60 l 220 70 l 230 70 l 230 60 m 230 60 m 200 340 l 200 350 l 210 350 l 210 340 m 210 340 m 210 350 l 210 360 l 220 360 l 220 350 m 220 350 m 220 320 l 220 330 l 230 330 l 230 320 m 230 320 m 270 50 l 270 60 l 280 60 l 280 50 m 280 50 m 120 300 l 120 310 l 130 310 l 130 300 m 130 300 m 180 200 l 180 210 l 190 210 l 190 200 m 190 200 m 290 280 l 290 290 l 300 290 l 300 280 m 300 280 m 190 250 l 190 260 l 200 260 l 200 250 m 200 250 m 170 90 l 170 100 l 180 100 l 180 90 m 180 90 m 40 100 l 40 110 l 50 110 l 50 100 m 50 100 m 280 70 l 280 80 l 290 80 l 290 70 m 290 70 m 310 340 l 310 350 l 320 350 l 320 340 m 320 340 m 320 290 l 320 300 l 330 300 l 330 290 m 330 290 m 60 80 l 60 90 l 70 90 l 70 80 m 70 80 m 100 100 l 100 110 l 110 110 l 110 100 m 110 100 m 340 70 l 340 80 l 350 80 l 350 70 m 350 70 m 80 220 l 80 230 l 90 230 l 90 220 m 90 220 m 230 300 l 230 310 l 240 310 l 240 300 m 240 300 m 200 250 l 200 260 l 210 260 l 210 250 m 210 250 m 100 280 l 100 290 l 110 290 l 110 280 m 110 280 m 250 200 l 250 210 l 260 210 l 260 200 m 260 200 m 270 360 l 270 370 l 280 370 l 280 360 m 280 360 m 230 40 l 230 50 l 240 50 l 240 40 m 240 40 m 210 200 l 210 210 l 220 210 l 220 200 m 220 200 m 220 270 l 220 280 l 230 280 l 230 270 m 230 270 m 120 50 l 120 60 l 130 60 l 130 50 m 130 50 m 190 220 l 190 230 l 200 230 l 200 220 m 200 220 m 40 330 l 40 340 l 50 340 l 50 330 m 50 330 m 280 140 l 280 150 l 290 150 l 290 140 m 290 140 m 310 270 l 310 280 l 320 280 l 320 270 m 320 270 m 320 200 l 320 210 l 330 210 l 330 200 m 330 200 m 300 40 l 300 50 l 310 50 l 310 40 m 310 40 m 70 340 l 70 350 l 80 350 l 80 340 m 80 340 m 330 190 l 330 200 l 340 200 l 340 190 m 340 190 m 200 160 l 200 170 l 210 170 l 210 160 m 210 160 m 250 290 l 250 300 l 260 300 l 260 290 m 260 290 m 230 130 l 230 140 l 240 140 l 240 130 m 240 130 m 210 130 l 210 140 l 220 140 l 220 130 m 220 130 m 240 60 l 240 70 l 250 70 l 250 60 m 250 60 m 220 180 l 220 190 l 230 190 l 230 180 m 230 180 m 270 270 l 270 280 l 280 280 l 280 270 m 280 270 m 250 70 l 250 80 l 260 80 l 260 70 m 260 70 m 360 90 l 360 100 l 370 100 l 370 90 m 370 90 m 130 90 l 130 100 l 140 100 l 140 90 m 140 90 m 270 170 l 270 180 l 280 180 l 280 170 m 280 170 m 140 60 l 140 70 l 150 70 l 150 60 m 150 60 m 190 310 l 190 320 l 200 320 l 200 310 m 200 310 m 150 150 l 150 160 l 160 160 l 160 150 m 160 150 m 40 240 l 40 250 l 50 250 l 50 240 m 50 240 m 280 210 l 280 220 l 290 220 l 290 210 m 290 210 m 50 210 l 50 220 l 60 220 l 60 210 m 60 210 m 290 160 l 290 170 l 300 170 l 300 160 m 300 160 m 190 50 l 190 60 l 200 60 l 200 50 m 200 50 m 60 260 l 60 270 l 70 270 l 70 260 m 70 260 m 300 150 l 300 160 l 310 160 l 310 150 m 310 150 m 50 150 l 50 160 l 60 160 l 60 150 m 60 150 m 340 170 l 340 180 l 350 180 l 350 170 m 350 170 m 80 40 l 80 50 l 90 50 l 90 40 m 90 40 m 40 360 l 40 370 l 50 370 l 50 360 m 50 360 m 350 120 l 350 130 l 360 130 l 360 120 m 360 120 m 330 120 l 330 130 l 340 130 l 340 120 m 340 120 m 100 140 l 100 150 l 110 150 l 110 140 m 110 140 m 340 270 l 340 280 l 350 280 l 350 270 m 350 270 m 230 180 l 230 190 l 240 190 l 240 180 m 240 180 m 110 230 l 110 240 l 120 240 l 120 230 m 120 230 m 350 260 l 350 270 l 360 270 l 360 260 m 360 260 m 220 130 l 220 140 l 230 140 l 230 130 m 230 130 m 250 160 l 250 170 l 260 170 l 260 160 m 260 160 m 120 190 l 120 200 l 130 200 l 130 190 m 130 190 m 270 140 l 270 150 l 280 150 l 280 140 m 280 140 m 140 170 l 140 180 l 150 180 l 150 170 m 150 170 m 130 200 l 130 210 l 140 210 l 140 200 m 140 200 m 280 280 l 280 290 l 290 290 l 290 280 m 290 280 m 170 140 l 170 150 l 180 150 l 180 140 m 180 140 m 60 210 l 60 220 l 70 220 l 70 210 m 70 210 m 40 50 l 40 60 l 50 60 l 50 50 m 50 50 m 50 160 l 50 170 l 60 170 l 60 160 m 60 160 m 80 190 l 80 200 l 90 200 l 90 190 m 90 190 m 320 320 l 320 330 l 330 330 l 330 320 m 330 320 m 60 150 l 60 160 l 70 160 l 70 150 m 70 150 m 90 180 l 90 190 l 100 190 l 100 180 m 100 180 m 80 250 l 80 260 l 90 260 l 90 250 m 90 250 m 110 120 l 110 130 l 120 130 l 120 120 m 120 120 m 240 200 l 240 210 l 250 210 l 250 200 m 250 200 m 200 200 l 200 210 l 210 210 l 210 200 m 210 200 m 250 250 l 250 260 l 260 260 l 260 250 m 260 250 m 360 230 l 360 240 l 370 240 l 370 230 m 370 230 m 220 300 l 220 310 l 230 310 l 230 300 m 230 300 m 270 70 l 270 80 l 280 80 l 280 70 m 280 70 m 180 260 l 180 270 l 190 270 l 190 260 m 190 260 m 190 270 l 190 280 l 200 280 l 200 270 m 200 270 m 150 350 l 150 360 l 160 360 l 160 350 m 160 350 m 40 280 l 40 290 l 50 290 l 50 280 m 50 280 m 320 310 l 320 320 l 330 320 l 330 310 m 330 310 m 60 60 l 60 70 l 70 70 l 70 60 m 70 60 m 100 80 l 100 90 l 110 90 l 110 80 m 110 80 m 80 320 l 80 330 l 90 330 l 90 320 m 90 320 m 90 210 l 90 220 l 100 220 l 100 210 m 100 210 m 240 350 l 240 360 l 250 360 l 250 350 m 250 350 m 100 340 l 100 350 l 110 350 l 110 340 m 110 340 m 210 260 l 210 270 l 220 270 l 220 260 m 220 260 m 260 330 l 260 340 l 270 340 l 270 330 m 270 330 m 270 280 l 270 290 l 280 290 l 280 280 m 280 280 m 120 70 l 120 80 l 130 80 l 130 70 m 130 70 m 360 40 l 360 50 l 370 50 l 370 40 m 370 40 m 130 60 l 130 70 l 140 70 l 140 60 m 140 60 m 140 290 l 140 300 l 150 300 l 150 290 m 150 290 m 190 320 l 190 330 l 200 330 l 200 320 m 200 320 m 150 240 l 150 250 l 160 250 l 160 240 m 160 240 m 40 350 l 40 360 l 50 360 l 50 350 m 50 350 m 290 130 l 290 140 l 300 140 l 300 130 m 300 130 m 170 260 l 170 270 l 180 270 l 180 260 m 180 260 m 320 220 l 320 230 l 330 230 l 330 220 m 330 220 m 60 330 l 60 340 l 70 340 l 70 330 m 70 330 m 70 40 l 70 50 l 80 50 l 80 40 m 80 40 m 350 170 l 350 180 l 360 180 l 360 170 m 360 170 m 90 300 l 90 310 l 100 310 l 100 300 m 100 300 m 330 170 l 330 180 l 340 180 l 340 170 m 340 170 m 340 220 l 340 230 l 350 230 l 350 220 m 350 220 m 230 150 l 230 160 l 240 160 l 240 150 m 240 150 m 110 240 l 110 250 l 120 250 l 120 240 m 120 240 m 260 240 l 260 250 l 270 250 l 270 240 m 270 240 m 240 160 l 240 170 l 250 170 l 250 160 m 250 160 m 270 210 l 270 220 l 280 220 l 280 210 m 280 210 m 260 180 l 260 190 l 270 190 l 270 180 m 270 180 m 270 190 l 270 200 l 280 200 l 280 190 m 280 190 m 140 40 l 140 50 l 150 50 l 150 40 m 150 40 m 120 200 l 120 210 l 130 210 l 130 200 m 130 200 m 150 170 l 150 180 l 160 180 l 160 170 m 160 170 m 160 180 l 160 190 l 170 190 l 170 180 m 170 180 m 50 270 l 50 280 l 60 280 l 60 270 m 60 270 m 60 240 l 60 250 l 70 250 l 70 240 m 70 240 m 300 130 l 300 140 l 310 140 l 310 130 m 310 130 m 40 160 l 40 170 l 50 170 l 50 160 m 50 160 m 70 130 l 70 140 l 80 140 l 80 130 m 80 130 m 80 60 l 80 70 l 90 70 l 90 60 m 90 60 m 60 180 l 60 190 l 70 190 l 70 180 m 70 180 m 350 140 l 350 150 l 360 150 l 360 140 m 360 140 m 330 100 l 330 110 l 340 110 l 340 100 m 340 100 m 200 90 l 200 100 l 210 100 l 210 90 m 210 90 m 100 120 l 100 130 l 110 130 l 110 120 m 110 120 m 340 250 l 340 260 l 350 260 l 350 250 m 350 250 m 250 360 l 250 370 l 260 370 l 260 360 m 260 360 m 240 150 l 240 160 l 250 160 l 250 150 m 250 150 m 330 360 l 330 370 l 340 370 l 340 360 m 340 360 m 250 140 l 250 150 l 260 150 l 260 140 m 260 140 m 210 300 l 210 310 l 220 310 l 220 300 m 220 300 m 130 160 l 130 170 l 140 170 l 140 160 m 140 160 m 270 80 l 270 90 l 280 90 l 280 80 m 280 80 m 130 260 l 130 270 l 140 270 l 140 260 m 140 260 m 280 300 l 280 310 l 290 310 l 290 300 m 290 300 m 180 170 l 180 180 l 190 180 l 190 170 m 190 170 m 160 90 l 160 100 l 170 100 l 170 90 m 170 90 m 140 250 l 140 260 l 150 260 l 150 250 m 150 250 m 190 120 l 190 130 l 200 130 l 200 120 m 200 120 m 170 120 l 170 130 l 180 130 l 180 120 m 180 120 m 150 280 l 150 290 l 160 290 l 160 280 m 160 280 m 300 200 l 300 210 l 310 210 l 310 200 m 310 200 m 40 70 l 40 80 l 50 80 l 50 70 m 50 70 m 280 40 l 280 50 l 290 50 l 290 40 m 290 40 m 70 180 l 70 190 l 80 190 l 80 180 m 80 180 m 90 160 l 90 170 l 100 170 l 100 160 m 100 160 m 330 350 l 330 360 l 340 360 l 340 350 m 340 350 m 100 70 l 100 80 l 110 80 l 110 70 m 110 70 m 340 320 l 340 330 l 350 330 l 350 320 m 350 320 m 230 290 l 230 300 l 240 300 l 240 290 m 240 290 m 240 220 l 240 230 l 250 230 l 250 220 m 250 220 m 210 230 l 210 240 l 220 240 l 220 230 m 220 230 m 360 250 l 360 260 l 370 260 l 370 250 m 370 250 m 220 280 l 220 290 l 230 290 l 230 280 m 230 280 m 270 330 l 270 340 l 280 340 l 280 330 m 280 330 m 120 340 l 120 350 l 130 350 l 130 340 m 130 340 m 360 150 l 360 160 l 370 160 l 370 150 m 370 150 m 290 320 l 290 330 l 300 330 l 300 320 m 300 320 m 190 210 l 190 220 l 200 220 l 200 210 m 200 210 m 40 300 l 40 310 l 50 310 l 50 300 m 50 300 m 320 250 l 320 260 l 330 260 l 330 250 m 330 250 m 60 40 l 60 50 l 70 50 l 70 40 m 70 40 m 300 90 l 300 100 l 310 100 l 310 90 m 310 90 m 330 280 l 330 290 l 340 290 l 340 280 m 340 280 m 70 330 l 70 340 l 80 340 l 80 330 m 80 330 m 80 340 l 80 350 l 90 350 l 90 340 m 90 340
我们会另想办法
We'll work something out.
再艰难的路我们挺过来了
We've been through worse.
林肯  对不起
Linc, I'm so sorry.
对不起  兄弟
I'm so sorry, brother.
林肯  找到奥玛  他...
Lincoln? Find Omar. He...
什么
‭What?
我听不到  你说什么
I can't hear you. What?